https://www.themusiczoo.com/9160836/policies/11172163.html

Privacy Policy
Return to Homepage
Thank you for visiting our site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at www.themusiczoo.com. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Collection of Information We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists. Unsubscribing from our newsletter can easily be accomplished by clicking "unsubscribe" in the email, or by contacting us.
Cookie/Tracking Technology The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of Information We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. We will not sell your information to any other entity for 3rd party marketing or any other reason.
Commitment to Data Security Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Certain privacy laws around the world, including the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, EU-GDPR principles, and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles (the “Privacy Shield Principles”) provide users with certain rights related to their personal information collected. Consistent with those laws, The Music Zoo gives you the choice of accessing, editing, or removing certain information, as well as choices about how we contact you. You may change or correct your Music Zoo account information through your account settings. You can also request the deletion of the personal information in your account.
Personal Information You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to process your order without this information. We do not sell your private information to outside parties.
Personal information we collect Personal information comes to us in many different ways, such as: • Purchase a product from us • Register on the website • Submit questions • Email us • Submit pricing requests on the checkout page • Enter a drawing or contest.
Personal data we may collect (if applicable) includes the following: • Name • Gender • Username • Password • Email address • Postal address • Phone number and/or mobile number • Products viewed or purchased
Your credit card number, cvv, etc, is held securely by our credit card processor which cannot be accessed by The Music Zoo.
The CCPA provides California residents with the following additional rights:Right to Know – California residents may request disclosure of the specific pieces and/or categories of personal information that the business has collected about them, the categories of sources for that personal information, the business or commercial purposes for collecting the information, the categories of personal information that we have disclosed, and the categories of third parties with which the information was shared.Right to Opt-Out – The Music Zoo does not sell information to 3rd parties, however to the extent that we “sell” personal information as that term is defined under the CCPA, California residents are entitled to opt-out of the “sale” of data at any time. We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your rights, including denying you goods or services, providing you with a different level or quality of services, or charging you different prices or rates for services, but, depending on your request, we may not be able to process or complete your order. You can exercise any of the rights above by contacting us at sales@themusiczoo.com or by submitting a request here.
Important: Why do I have to accept the terms of this privacy policy? This Privacy Policy provides you with all information necessary (in an easily accessible way) to make an informed choice as to whether to use this website and to send your personal information to us or not. Therefore, by browsing this website and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our Processing of your indirect personal information (cookies, connection, and system information) in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. If you wish to register on the website or ask us to provide a service to you (i.e., a product purchase, newsletter or new product details, etc.) we will need additional direct personal information (e.g., name, address and email address) from you. If you are under [16], we ask you to contact your parent or legal guardian, for your express consent to collect and use this Personal Information. This Personal Information will be used only for the purposes for which you gave it to us.
Privacy Contact Information If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By e-mail: sales@themusiczoo.com By Phone: 516-626-9292 We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted here.
This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply.
Return to Homepage
Opens external website in a new window.
Opens in a new window.
Opens external website.
Customer information - The Music Zoo - Checkout
